Danielle Humilde

UX/UI Designer

d.humilde@outlook.com

LinkedIn

SUMMARY

My passion for design is to create inclusive and diverse interfaces for a wide array of user experiences. I have professional experience in digital marketing and the Design field working contracts and freelancing. I have a certificate in UX/UI Design and Research from OCAD University. With my diverse educational background in Political Science, Digital Marketing and Design, I believe that it widens my perspective for a more holistic understanding of the end user.

DESIGN PROJECTS

SUBTLE-T App Design Concept

An app made to help those who are experiencing domestic abuse and need access to resources
they need to help them determine a course of action and a safety plan to leave their situation
discreetly

TORONTO TUBE App Design Concept

 An app for Presto card users to adapt contactless payment similar to Apple Pay to enhance app capabilities

WORK EXPERIENCE

MARSH MCLENNAN Digital Marketing Specialist September 2021 - Current

- Regional Digital Manager for Canada managing Dotcom/DotCA affairs via AEM
- Manage all content being uploaded to the Canadian website (English and French copies); and work closely with the global team to ensure all content is up to brand standards
- Plan and upload relevant content for campaigns in various industries represented by other marketers on the team
- Design analytic reports via Data Studio of how the Canadian website is performing and identify areas to enhance user experience on the website

BETH MARICIC DESIGN Digital Design Manager June 2020 - September 2021

- $\bullet \ \ \text{Managed and create custom webpages to present design concepts for interior design clients}$
- Developed new marketing assets by redesigning website literature, landing pages, and social media marketing campaigns
- Designed and test different platforms (Instagram, Facebook, YouTube, Spotify) for marketing campaigns to evaluate ROI optimisation with strict campaign budget

DAVIDS & DELAAT Marketing, Operations & Communications October 2020 - March 2021

- Lead several campaigns and ongoing projects at the firm, such as website enhancement and redesign, TV/radio, billboard, and target/retargeting marketing campaigns
- · Managed and executed owned social media calendar and brand redesign on multiple platforms
- Studied current real estate market trends to generate relevant content during lull months of real
 estate to keep audience engaged

FREELANCE UX/UI Design and Digital Marketing June 2019 - September 2021

- Consulted with various small to mid-sized businesses to review current products and services, to solve user needs and business challenges through Market Research, Campaign Analysis, Visual Design, and Website Architecture
- Businesses ranged from sustainable product brand to defence law firm

EDUCATION

OCAD UNIVERSITY UX/UI Design and Research August 2021

- Develop UX/UI research skills and design implementation with a focus on User Experience Design and Development
- Micro-certification in Ideation & Prototyping, and Empathy & Social Insight for Human Centric Design

GEORGE BROWN COLLEGE Post Graduate Digital Media Marketing October 2020

 Obtained online certifications for various softwares such as Hootsuite, Brandwatch and Google Analytics for digital media marketing strategies

UNIVERSITY OF WESTERN ONTARIO BA Political Science June 2019

- Varsity Rowing and Golf
- VP Communications of Political Science Association

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Adobe Experience Manager (AEM)

Brandwatch

Canva

Facebook and Instagram Business Manager

Figma

Google Ads, Analytics and Data Studio

Hootsuite

HTML/CSS

KV Core

Mailchimp

Microsoft Office Suite

Miro

Squarespace

Word Press